<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help_welcome">Welcome to the Risk Help File!</string>
	<string name="help_start">To begin, choose what you would like to calculate.
		\nThe app assumes that you are the attacker.</string>
	<string name="help_option0_h">\"What are my odds of winning this fight, 
		dynamically?\"</string>
	<string name="help_option0_b">Select this option if you know how many 
		attackers there are and how many defenders there are.\nPress 
		\"Calculate\" and the attacker\'s chance of winning will be displayed.
		\nAs the dice are rolled and armies are lost, you can press the buttons
		to see how your chances of victory are progressing.</string>
	<string name="help_option1_h">\"How many armies do I need to win this fight?\"</string>
	<string name="help_option1_b">Select this option if you know how many 
		defenders your opponent has and you want to know how many armies you 
		should attack with.\nPress \"Calculate\" and a graph will appear.</string>
	<string name="help_read_graph_h">Reading The Graph:</string>
	<string name="help_read_graph_b">The horizontal axis indicates a number of armies. 
		The vertical axis indicates a percent chance of victory.\nAs the number
		of attacking armies increases, the odds of winning increases.\nSelect what you
		believe to be a reasonable chance of victory, then find the 
		corresponding number of armies.</string>
	<string name="help_use_graph_h">Using The Graph:</string>
	<string name="help_use_graph_b">Slide to scroll\nPinch to zoom
		\nLong Press to reset zoom</string>
	<string name="help_option2_h">\"What are my odds of completing this campaign?\"</string>
	<string name="help_option2_b">Select this option if you will be attacking several 
		territories in a row.\nIn the first box, enter the number of attackers. In the 
		second, enter the number of defenders that are in the first territory. Press \"Add 
		Row\".\nFor now, ignore the new attackers box.\nIn the second defenders box, insert 
		the number of defenders in the second territory.\nIf there is a
		third territory, press \"Add Row\" and enter the number of defenders in that 
		territory.\nRepeat for each defending territory.\nPress \"Calculate!\".\nThis will 
		display the chance of taking each territory and the expected remaining armies when 
		that territory is taken.\nTap the first row.\nThis will take you to the dynamic 
		fight screen, with the text boxes already filled out. Press the buttons as the 
		battle progresses. At any time, press the back button to return to the campaign 
		screen. When you do, the row you clicked will be updated with the information from 
		the battle screen, and every row will be updated with new odds.\nIn addition, a new 
		attackers box will appear for the next row. If you pressed back while the defender 
		had zero armies, then the next row will be updated with the number of attackers, 
		less the one that must stay behind.\nRepeat this until you\'re satisfied.</string>
	<string name="help_risiko_h">\"Use RisiKo rules\"</string>
	<string name="help_risiko_b">In the preferences menu, you can set the app to use RisiKo 
		(also known as European) rules. With these rules, the defender can roll three dice, 
		not just two. This means in a 3v3 throw, either side could lose up to 3 units at a 
		time. This favors (under RisiKo rules, favours) the defender.</string>
	<string name="help_estimation_h">Blue Numbers</string>
	<string name="help_estimation_b">Blue Numbers indicate that the value is an estimate, 
		not a direct calculation. Direct calculations become very expensive with large 
		numbers, such as those where the attacker or defender armies are larger than 1000. 
		Since these are not numbers likely to appear in an actual Risk game, an estimate 
		will suffice. If you would like an actual calculation, visit PhoenixRamen.net.
		</string>
	<string name="proof_link">To see the proof of all calculations, click the proof link in the app menu.
		</string>
	<string name="support">For additional questions or to submit bug reports, 
		please email support@PhoenixRamen.net</string>
</resources>